Guide to the Cornell University International Agriculture records, 1952-1980.
Cornell University International Agriculture records
- Series XIII. University of the Philippines - Cornell University Graduate Education Program(UP-Cornell) - Chronological File
  - Correspondence University Directors of IAD Programs, 1966-1970 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - AUSUDIAP (Association of U. S. University Directors of International Agriculture Programs), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - AUSUDIAP, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - AUSUDIAP, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - AUSUDIAP Executive Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - AUSUDIAP - Second Meeting - Minnesota, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - AUSUDIAP - Purdue University, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - AUSUDIAP - 4th Annual Conference - Washington, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - AUSUDIAP - Florida, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - AUSUDIAP - University of Illinois, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - AUSUDIAP - University of Illinois, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - AUSUDIAP - University of Illinois, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - AUSUDIAP - Hawaii, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - AUSUDIAP - Background Papers - Washington, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - AUSUDIAP - Washington, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - AUSUDIAP - Program Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - AUSUDIAP - Treasurer, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - AUSUDIAP - Secretary-Treasurer, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Analysis of Proposed International Development and Humanitarian Assistance Act, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Center of International Studies, 1971-1976 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Center of International Studies Rural Development Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Center of International Studies Rural Development Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - International Agricultural Development Conference, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - International Agricultural Development Conference, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - International Agricultural Research Foundation, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - International Agricultural Research Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - IAD - Role of the College of Agriculture, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - IAD - Advisory Committee, 1967-1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - IAD - Advisory Committee Agenda and Minutes, 1968-1974 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - International Education Act - McGovern Proposal, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - International Education Act - McGovern Proposal, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - IAD - Miscellaneous Publications, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - IAD - Advisory Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - IAD - State Positions, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - IAD - Present Status and Future Plans, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - IAD - Visiting Professor Program, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Analysis for the Need of International Agriculture Program, 1962-1967 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Analysis for the Need of International Agriculture Program, 1962-1967 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - International Education, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - United Nations Education in India, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - United Nations Education in India, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Ashford - CIS (Center for International Studies), 1964-1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Muller - CIS (Center for International Studies), 1964-1969 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - CIS Announcement, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Visiting Appointments, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - CIS Budget, 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - CIS - Suggestions for Directorship, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - CIS Executive Committee, 1963-1969 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - CIS Executive Committee Minutes, 1962-1970 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Proposal to Ford Foundation for Transitional Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - CIS Program Committee, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - CIS Program Committee Minutes, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - CIS Request to Ford Foundation for International Agricultural Development, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - CIS - Ten Year Projections, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - CIS Annual Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - CIS Annual Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - International Development Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - International Development Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Program Director's Meetings, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Peace Corps International Agriculture Forum, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Peace Corps International Agriculture Forum, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Pest Management and Plant Resistance Proposal to Rockefeller Foundation, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - SUNY, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - SUNY International Studies, 1964-1972 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Report on Campus Self-Survey of International Education Involvement, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - SUNY International Program Office, 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Steps Seminar, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Soybean Project, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Tropical Agriculture, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Henry B. Wu Memorial Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Hubert G. Zandstra, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Russian Visitors to Cornell, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - US - USSR Exchanges, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - USSR-Washington D.C., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - USSR-Washington D.C., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - World Food Supplies, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - World Food Supplies, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - World Food Supplies, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - World Food Congress, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - World Food Congress, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - World Food Congress, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - World Food and Agricultural Research Education and Development Act, 1966-1968 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - IAD (International Agricultural Development) Faculty, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Solon Barraclough, 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Loy Crowder, 1965-1976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Loy Crowder, 1965-1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Matthew Drosdoff, 1965-1975 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Donald Freebairn, 1966-1976 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Paul Leagans, 1964-1975 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Paul Leagans, 1964-1975 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Robert McDowell, 1965-1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Robert McDowell, 1965-1975 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - John Mellor, 1966-1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - John Mellor, 1966-1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Mellor AID Contracts, 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Mellor Reports, Proposals, Publications, 1956-1969 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Mellor Reports, Proposals, Publications, 1968-1970 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Mellor Reports, Proposals, Publications, 1965-1975 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Mellor Final Research Report, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - International Development Conference at Blacksburg, Virginia, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Symposium Communication Strategies for Rural Development, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Research Report on the Food Economy of Malaysia and Brunei, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Food Balance Sheet as a Parameter of Tropical Food Economies, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Professor Poleman, 1966-1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Professor Poleman, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Professor Poleman, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Robert Polson, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - David Thurston, 1967-1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - David Thurston, 1972-1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Armand Van Wambeke, 1974-1977 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Frank Young, 1965-1974 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Frank Young - Community Growth in Southwestern Puerto Rico, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - International Agriculture Program Advisory Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Memos from the Dean, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Memos from George Kent, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Memos from Director of Research, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Dean Call, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Associate Dean Egner, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Deans and Directors, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Operations, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Public Policy Coordinator, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Keith Kennedy, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Development Fund, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Agricultural Engineering, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Agronomy, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Animal Science, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Bailey Hortorium, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Communication Arts, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Communications' Director Search, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Ecology, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Education, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Entomology, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Extension, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Extension County Agents, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Floriculture, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Landscape Architecture, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Food Science, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Geneva, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Instruction, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Mann Library, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Media Services, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Natural Resources, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Placement Office, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Plant Breeding, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Biometrics, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Plant Pathology, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Pomology, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Poultry, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Research, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Rural Sociology, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Harold Capener, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Vegetable Crops, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence - A, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Advisory Council, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Africa, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - AgPAC (Agriculture and Life Sciences Positive Action Council), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - AID, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - American Farm School, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - B, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Barbados, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bethany College - West Virginia, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Board for International Food and Agricultural Development, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Biological Sciences, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Botswana, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Boyce Thompson Institute, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Brazil, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - C, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Camel Breeders, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - CIS (Center for International Studies), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - CIS Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - CIS - Rural Development Committee, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - CALS Computing Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Relations Activity, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - D, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - DIALS, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - E, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - CALS Environmental Studies, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - F, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Facilities Coordinator - Herbert Pallesen, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - FAO (Food and Agriculture Organization), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Ford Foundation, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - France, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Fulbright-Hays, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - G, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Graduate School, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Graduate Degree List, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - H, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Human Ecology, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Humphrey Fellowships, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - I, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - IAD Publications and Policies, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - International Agriculture Rural Development, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - IARD (International Agriculture Rural Development Courses and Lectures), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - India, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - ILR (Industrial and Labor Relations), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Indonesia, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - International Agriculture College Position Paper, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Inter-American Development Bank, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Inter-American Development Resources Management Training Center, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - International Education Committee, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - IRRI, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - International Science and Education Council, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - International Science and Education Council, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Israel, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Japan, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Jurzykowski Foundation, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - K, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Kenya, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - L, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Land Use and Natural Resources Inventories, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Leonardo Da Vinci Society, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lomba, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - M, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Mexico, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - N, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - NASULGC, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - NASULGC, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - NASULGC International Letter, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Nebraska Workshop, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Northeast Directors of International Agricultural Development, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Nutritional Sciences, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - O, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Ombudsman, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - P, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Peace Corps, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Pest Management, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Philippines, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Professors at Large, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - R, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Rees - Dean of City University of New York, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Roots and Tubers, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - S, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Scholarships, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Searca, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Soviet Union, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Science, Technology, Society, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - SUNY, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Swaziland, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - T, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Thailand, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Tinker Foundation, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Traveling Fellowships, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - U, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Unions, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - United Nations Development Program, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - United Way, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - USDA, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence - V, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Vet College, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence - W, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Women in Development, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Women in Development Workshop, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - World Bank, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - World Food Issues, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence - X, Y, and Z, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Zambia, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Ford Thesis Research Evaluation Panel, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Bailey, L. Conner Jr., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Kam, Suan-Pheng, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Lee, Seon, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Pachico, Douglas, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Ferroni, Marco A., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Teri, James M., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Briceno, Oscar, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Buyukcolak, Unal, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Calkins, Peter H., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Garcia, Philip, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Gardner, George R., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Kanchanachitra, Surapol, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Knauft, David, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Monardes, Alfonso, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Posner, Josh, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Sepulveda, Sergio, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - St. Louis, David G., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Tschanz, Arnold T., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Terasart, Thanya, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Allaway, James D., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Danso, Seth K. A., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Kass, Donald C., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Ngongi, Amos G. N., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Wolf, James M., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Sharma, Prakash Narayan, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Allaway, James D., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Alleyne, Patrick A., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Belt, Juan A. B.., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Krausz, Joseph P., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Bravo, Alonso, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Deutsch, James A., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Ireson, W. Randall, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Schlegel, Charles C., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Unsal, Fahri, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Snipper, Reuben, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Annan, Akweley, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Ashby, Jacqueline Anne, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Chambas, Mohamed IBN, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - de Gonneville, Brigitte, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - McRae, Stephen D., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Odeywmi, Olu, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Gwynn, Douglas L., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Healy, Kevin J., 1974 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Kanawan, Keawta, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Okezie, Baldwin Onuma, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Sada, Guillermo, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Hixson, Robert S., 1973 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Jantzi, Vernon E., 1973 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Kretchmer, Paul Jay, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Liu, Carol Bei Wei, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Mensah, Eric Adzetey, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Patterson, William, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Putz, Francis Edward Jr., 1979 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Roseberry, Sidney C., 1979 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Showers, Kate, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Sisaye, Seleshi, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Weinstock, Joseph, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report to Ford Foundation - Graduate Student Research Abroad, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Thesis Research Abroad, 1977-1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Ford Foundation - Graduate Fellowships for Thesis Research Abroad, 1971-1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Preliminary Proposals to Ford Foundation, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence - Philippines, 1974-1979 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - General Policies CU Professors Participating in UP-Cornell Program, 1965-1967 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Development Program for the College of Agriculture University of the Philippines, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Guidelines for Ph.D Thesis Research for Asian Graduate Students, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for Continuation of UP-Cornell Graduate Education Program, 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - UPLB (University of Philippines-Los Banos), IRRI (International Rice Research Institute) and Cornell Proposal, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Candidates - UPLB - Cornell Graduate Education Program, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Vitae - IRRI - UPLB Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Ford Foundation Philippines, 1964-1976 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Ford Grant, 1972-1977 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Philippines Publication - Poultry and Egg Consumption Patterns, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Philippines Publication - Meat Consumption, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Philippines Publication - Sea Food Consumption, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Philippines Publication - World and Far East Trade in Livestock and Poultry Products, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Philippines Publication - Improved Facilities for Loading Hogs Aboard Ships, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Philippines Publication - Cereal Consumption, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Philippines Publication - Feasibility of a Modern Livestock Processing Plant, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Philippines Publication - Optimal Locations and Sizes of Livestock Processing Plants, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Philippines Publication - A Livestock Aucton Market, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Philippines Publication - Consumption Patterns for Sea Foods, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Philippines Publication - A Rice Futures Market, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Philippines Publication - Marketing Tools for the Philippines, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Philippines Publication - Consumption Patterns for Dairy Products, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Philippines Publication - Consumption Patterns for Selected Fruits, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Philippines Publication - Potential Export Markets and Rrstraints for Philippine Livestock, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Philippines Publication - Fresh Milk Marketing in the Philippines, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Philippines Publication - Bangus Marketing, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Philippines Publication - Regional Consumption Patterns for Major Foods, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Philippines Publication - Feasibility of a Special Boat for Shipping Live Animals, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Philippines Publication - Lanzones Marketing, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Philippines Publication - Income and Food Consumption, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Philippines Publication - Summary of Four Economic Surveys of Food Consumption, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Philippines Publication - Some Aspects of Exporting Philippine Mangoes, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Philippines Publication - Regional Consumption Partterns for Cereals, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Philippines Publication - Potential Demand and Supply of Fresh Milk, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Philippines Publication - Cantaloupe Marketing, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Philippines Publication - Hog Marketing Practices, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Philippines Publication - Papaya Marketing, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Philippines Publication - Household Inventories, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Philippines Publication - Production and Marketing of Sorghum, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Philippines Publication - Income and Food Consumption, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Philippines Publication - Summary of Three Economic Surveys, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Philippines Publication - Feasibility of a Feed Mill, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Philippines Publication - Fresh Milk Potentials, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Philippines Publication - A Model Public Market, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Philippines Publication - A Buffer Stock Scheme for Rice and Corn, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Marketing Reports, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Masagana 99 Rice Program, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Lawrence Darrah, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Philippine-U.S. Workshop on Food and Nutrition, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - U.S.-Philippine Workshop on Scientific and Technological Cooperation, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Reeshon Feuer, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - National Food and Agriculture Council, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Philippine Land Reform, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Philippine Council for Agricultural Research, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Foundaton Quarterly, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - SEARCA (Southeast Asian Regional Center for Graduate Study and Research in Agriculture), 1966-1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - VISAYAS State College of Agriculture - Baybay, Leyte, 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - F.A.Bernardo, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Lito Calo, 1968-1974 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - International Bank - Building Program, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Review of Los Banos Project, 1968-1971 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - UPCA Accounts, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Program at Los Banos, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - UPCA Participants Studying in U.S., 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)